{
   "quiz_one" : [
      {
         "question" : "HTML: What does HTML stand for?",
         "answer" : "Hyper Text Markup Language",
         "choices" : ["Hyper Text Markup Language", "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language", "Home Tool Markup Language"],
         "feedback" : "Correct answer is Hyper Text Markup Language"
      },
      {
         "question" : "HTML: Choose the correct HTML element for the largest heading:",
         "answer" : "<h1>",
         "choices" : ["<h6>","<h1>","<head>","<heading>"],
         "feedback" : "Correct answer is <h1>"
      },   
      {
         "question" : "CSS: What does CSS stand for?",
         "answer" : "Cascading Style Sheets",
         "choices" : ["Computer Style Sheets", "Creative Style Sheets","Colorful Style Sheets", "Cascading Style Sheets"],
         "feedback" : "Correct answer is Cascading Style Sheets"
      },
      {
         "question" : "CSS: Which HTML tag is used to define an internal style sheet?",
         "answer" : "<style>",
         "choices" : ["<style>","<script>","<css>"],
         "feedback" : "Correct answer is <style>"
      },  
      {
         "question" : "Javascript: Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
         "answer" : "<script>",
         "choices" : ["<js>","<scripting>","<script>","<javascript>"],
         "feedback" : "Correct answer is <script>"
      }      
   ],
   "quiz_two" : [
      {
         "question" : "Python: How do you insert COMMENTS in Python code?",
         "answer" : "#This is a comment",
         "choices" : ["/*This is a comment*/","#This is a comment","//This is a comment"],
         "feedback" : "Correct answer is #This is a comment"
      },
      {
         "question" : "Python: What is the correct way to create a function in Python?",
         "answer" : "def myFunction():",
         "choices" : ["def myFunction():","function myfunction():","create myFunction():"],
         "feedback" : "Correct answer is def myFunction():"
      },
      {
         "question" : "Java: Java is short for JavaScript.",
         "answer" : "False",
         "choices" : ["True","False"],
         "feedback" : "Correct answer is False"
      },
      {
         "question" : "Java: How do you insert COMMENTS in Java code?",
         "answer" : "// This is a comment",
         "choices" : ["/* This is a comment","// This is a comment", "# This is a comment"],
         "feedback" : "Correct answer is // This is a comment"
      },
      {
         "question" : "Java: The value of a string variable can be surrounded by single quotes.",
         "answer" : "False",
         "choices" : ["True","False"],
         "feedback" : "Correct answer is False"
      }
   ]
}
